fanfamilyexperience.com 2010-05-05

# Jonas Brothers | Fan Family Experience

FanFamilyExperience.com is committed to protecting your privacy and the security of all information and data on the Site. To demonstrate this commitment, FanFamilyExperience.com has adopted the following privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy") based on the principles of notice/awareness, choice/consent, access/participation and integrity/security in the collection and use of all information regarding the Site’s users and their activities at the Site. Please review this Privacy Policy each time you use the Site as it is subject to change at any time without notice to you. It is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. By accessing the Site you are indicating your agreement to this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site.

**Notice of the Site’s Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy tells you, among other things, what information and data is gathered and/or collected from you via the Site, how the that information and data may be used or disclosed, and the efforts made to protect that information and data. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**What Types of Information and Data are Collected and Why?**  
**Information and Data Submitted and Transmitted by You**

At times, the Site may have asked you to provide information and data about yourself in order to enhance and improve your use of the Site. This information and data may also be used by the Site’s host to contact you should the need arise or to respond appropriately to any request or question you have about the Site. Please note that the Site is not currently collecting any personal information or data.

**Information Collected by the Site’s Cookies**

The Site may make use of the "cookies" feature (described below) to help you use the Site more easily, and to help the FanFamilyExperience.com continuously improve the Site. A "cookie" is a small data file that the Site can send to the Internet browser you are using, which may then be stored on the hard drive or server of the Computer you are using to help the Site remember information about you when you return to the Site, such as your preferences for the Site or your account identifications. The Site’s cookies do not read data from the hard drive of the Computer you are using, read cookie files created by other Web sites, or track any personal information about you. You may have the option of setting the Internet browser (e.g., Google, Yahoo!, etc.) you are using to reject cookies however doing so may negatively impact upon the performance of the Site or restrict the FanFamilyExperience.com in better serving your use of the Site. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most Internet browsers will tell you how to prevent the Internet browser you are using from accepting new cookies, how to have the Internet browser notify you when a new cookie is received, or how to disable the cookie feature altogether.

Also, as the Site advertises the products and services of third parties, when you click on the banners or pop-ups or hyperlinks on the Site you must assume that information is being collected about you. FanFamilyExperience.com is not responsible for the use of any information and data collected in such a manner. You must also assume that (1) information and data will be collected from and about you and your Computer, (2) that cookies will usually be placed by Web sites on the hard drive of the Computer you are using, (3) that FanFamilyExperience.com has no control over what happens with such third party collection of your information and data, (4) that the FanFamilyExperience.com takes no responsibility, jointly and severally, for the advertisers’, sponsors’ and/or vendors’ Web sites, (5) that FanFamilyExperience.com, jointly or severally, is not responsible for downloads from third party advertisers, sponsors and vendors that contain viruses or worms or other computer code that causes harm to the Computer or software you are using, and (6) that FanFamilyExperience.com does not assume any responsibility for the information and data that is garnered from the click itself or that the advertiser, sponsor and/or vendor collects.

**Email Information**

If you send a person or entity an email from the Site, or if you email the Site’s URL, you must assume that some data is collected about IP address that you are using and/or your email address and that of the person or entity to whom you sent the email. You must assume that referred emails or Web site pages may appear to come from your email. You must accept full responsibility for referring emails and Web site pages to such person’s and entities agree to indemnify FanFamilyExperience.com for any damages, intentional or unintentional, that result from said emails and URL referrals.

**How Does the Site Use Information Collected by Cookies?**

FanFamilyExperience.com may use the information collected by cookies in an aggregated form to measure number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, and other relevant statistics. In general, the FanFamilyExperience.com collects this information to measure the overall visitor traffic, use of the Site and to improve the Content of the Site.

FanFamilyExperience.com uses your personally identifying information collected by cookies on the Site to identify you as a user of the Site and to assist and speed the completion of any transactions and dealings on the Site. FanFamilyExperience.com may use your email address to contact you directly regarding services or products that FanFamilyExperience.com believes may be of interest to you.

**Disclosure of Aggregate Information**

FanFamilyExperience.com may combine your personally identifying information, and information about your preferences, usage and activities, with those of all or a particular group of the Site’s users to prepare collective profiles of the Site’s users and their preferences, usage and activities for FanFamilyExperience.com internal use. For example, they may track the number of the Site’s users who view certain pages or use certain features on the Site or to track geographic trends. Such information and data, and other information FanFamilyExperience.com derives from the Site’s individual Users' information and data, allows FanFamilyExperience.com to continue to develop and provide you with quality information and data through more accurate marketing and advertising of the Site. FanFamilyExperience.com may share aggregated information concerning the Site’s users, without attribution of personal information, to FanFamilyExperience.com’s sponsors, vendors, advertisers, affiliates and other companies with whom FanFamilyExperience.com conducts business.

**General**

These Terms and Conditions, including the Privacy Policy, are governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of New York in the United States, without regard to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any disputes, controversies and claims arising under, in connection with, or out of these Terms and Conditions and/or this Privacy Policy shall lie exclusively with the state and federal courts within the State of New York. If any provision of these Terms and Conditions and/or this Privacy Policy is found to be invalid by a court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms and Conditions and/or this Privacy Policy, which shall remain in full force and effect. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL FanFamilyExperience.com, EITHER JOINTLY OR SEVERALLY, HAVE ANY LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR SPECIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND/OR THIS PRIVACY POLICY, HOWEVER OCCASIONED.
